And today, we are going to be testing
the new One Animate 2 model that has
released within the past few days. But
we're not only going to be testing this
model and seeing how good it is as an
upgrade over the original One Animate
that came out almost a year ago now.
We're also going to be comparing it to
what I consider the current king of
motion control within inside ComfyUI.
Today, I'm going to be testing Animate 2
against Scale 2, which has quietly taken
the spot as king for motion control in
ComfyUI over the past 2 months. So, we
are going to see if Animate 2 is
actually a threat or just another model
drop. So, taking a look at the output,
we can see that there is a slight color
difference, but for the most part, they
look pretty similar.
I'd say that Animate has some slight
clipping going on with the shirt and
artifacting going on towards the end of
the generation. So, I'm going to give
this one the scale, but they both look
pretty good. I think the quality from
Scale is a little bit better as well, so
definitely Scale. Now, I had to remove
the audio because there's copyrighted
music and I don't want to get copyright
striked, but to me, honestly, this is a
clear one. Scale is the easy winner
here. The Animate generation looks
pretty discolored for some reason,
whether that's the reference video doing
that or not, but Scale just does a good
job at covering it up. So, Scale is up
2-0. Now, it honestly took me a minute
to decide on this one, but I think I'm
going to go with Animate for this. Even
though it still has that slight
discoloration that's been going on
throughout the Animate generations, I
don't know why. The quality is just
better. The eyes look better. Pretty
much everything looks better, so I'm
going to go with Animate here. Even
though Scale does keep the background of
the original video, which is great
because there's actual people in the
background doing stuff in the gym, so it
looks very real, but unfortunately, the
quality of the person came out not so
great. That could probably be changed by
just running it